this island will make a wonderful Resort
for the aristocracy of robotropolis
hmm just smell that tropical air and so
quaint and rustic of course the village
will have to be relocated we can't let a
few Huts take up Prime real estate I
can't wait to get the resort built I'm
so sick of roughing it
I hope I can sleep in these primitive
conditions I want to look my best today
I'm going to the race you see two
hundred thousand I'm bringing these
peasants into the lap of luxury
Rosebud tea you wouldn't want the wrong
class of people to get in beautiful
robotnik's 2 crass to appreciate
anything like this you must get a real
bang out of your art collection not very
good at being Noble Sonia well actually
I am because well I'm nobility one of
the many pleasures of being a wealthy
Aristocrat who on Mobius Could It Be At
This Hour oh drag I'll have to get it
myself patience patience oh please don't
you think someone with my refinement
would be able to tell the difference
between a genuine artifact and some
silly little Bomb Dr Robotnik usually
asks my opinion on occasions like this
he's a brilliant man but socially he's
Trey Nouveau
where is that waiter soul to the lucky
bidder for a mere one million mobiles
you got this one cheap